welcome and thank you for choosing
prudential
as your preferred partner on this
journey we
are committed to punctual and reliable
service delivery
as well as quick response to all your
queries
we'd like to help you understand the
terms and conditions
of the policy benefits premiums
and modes of payment at the end of the
period you are saving for
you will receive the guaranteed amount
plus bonuses
this money will be paid to you or any
other person you have nominated
in the unfortunate event of loss of life
for permanent disability to you
prudential shall pay 50 percent
of the guaranteed about we shall also
take over payment of all future premiums
and in addition we shall pay the full
amount payable at the end of the period
you're saving for if you stop paying
premiums
before a period of either two years for
per dollar clients or three years
for pretty safe clients your cover will
cease and you will not be entitled to a
refund of premiums paid
after a period of two years for per
dollar clients
all three years for priority step
clients should you opt to cancel your
policy
prudential shall pay an amount known as
surrender value
please note that in the early stages of
your policy for example three years the
surrender payout is less than the total
premiums paid
where the policy has been enforced for
at least half the time you're saving for
the surrender amount payable is usually
more than the total premiums paid
surrendering a policy is not a
financially wise option
we would advise you to view this as a
last resolution
since it leads to loss of valuable
protection
abandonment of the original financial
goal and loss of money
we urge you to stay the course in your
quest to make the future of those you
love
better let's face life together tuli
naoi